The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
City Square
Sky Demon City
It's about to begin.
Who do you think will win this time ?
Jin Wuxu
Sky Demon City's Head Administrator
Rank 400 000 Demonic Energy
(Middle stage Ascendant)
Please welcome
the 6 Commanders-in-Chief of the Sky Demon Country !
Vice-Commander Xuan is about to be promoted.
Why are you making this face ?
Huang Commander-in-Chief
Rank 300 000 Demonic Energy
(Early stage Ascendant)
These youngsters are really lucky
for having a chance to get one of the two vacant positions.
But compared to you, who got here without a fight,
they still have a long way to go.
If you have time to make fun of me
then you should take a closer look at the rising talents.
Unless you want someone to replace you.
We pay respects to the Demon Emperor.
His Majesty is dealing with state affairs
and made a decree.
The winner shall be promoted to Vice Commander-in-Chief,
bestowed a dragon robe, a jade sash,
and the command of 3 armies.
All Demon Generals of the Sky Demon Country,
step forward !
The rules of the competition are:
Demon Generals fight first
and then their helpers.
Win both duels to win the match.
Win 4 matches to advance to the second round.
Remember that
those who kill a Demon General
will be executed.
Come forward,
Demon General Shi Xiao.
Shi Xiao !?
He's top 3 in strength !
Such a powerful aura !
No one will dare to challenge him, right ?
With his strength,
it's no wonder no one dares to fight.
If no challenger steps forward within 10 breaths,
Then I will...
I will !
Mu Yun
Demon General
Rank 150 000 Demonic Energy
(Late stage Soul Transformation)
This person cultivates
the Nine Deaths and Nine Lives.
He...
is no match for Shi Xiao.
The winner is decided.
The winner is Shi Xiao.
Now back down
and send your helper.
Tian Lui
Giant Spirit Sect disciple
Late stage Soul Transformation
This guy is strong,
I've seen him before.
He's a prodigy of the Giant Spirit Sect.
This fight will be worth watching.
According to the rules,
both duels need to be won.
Even if the helper wins this duel,
Mu Yun is still eliminated.
What's the point of this second duel ?
Let me show you
the Giant Spirit Sect's One Strength Breaks All Spells !
No...
No !
I won't fight...
I won't fight !
Demon Generals are protected by imperial decree
but helpers are pigs waiting to be slaughtered.
"Win both duels to win the match"...
This is clearly a slaughter fest for Demon Generals.
You won !
Demon General don't fight to the death
What do you think you're doing !?
so it's boring.
So you outsiders are here
for us to have some fun.
Mo Lihai,
come up.
We will settle
the debt from back then !
I lost to Mo Fei.
According to our agreement,
I can't fight today.
You,
come up here to die.
I'm not interested in a duel
where I can't kill.
Demon General Shi Xiao,
you won this match.
According to the rules,
you can't challenge others anymore.
Stand to the side.
Mo Lihai cannot fight
but you...
I will tear you apart !
You !
Come up.
Vice-Commander Xuan,
do you know this man ?
I don't.
However,
this young man will definitely place in the top 3.
He might even win.
A mere Peak Late stage Soul Transformation...
Even among Demon Generals, he's just average.
How can an outsider like him
possibly get first place ?
Since Vice-Commander Huang doesn't believe it,
shall we make a bet ?
If he does not win the competition,
my Heavenly Omen Flag
will be yours.
But if he wins,
I want your Mystic Yellow Pill.
Bet ?
So Vice-Commander Xuan is determined to gift me his Heavenly Omen Flag.
Fine,
I'll take that bet.
If he had also injured you,
you wouldn't be making fun of him.
I'll go !
Ao Di
Demon General
Rank 150 000 Demonic Energy
(Late stage Soul Transformation)
Mo Lihai cannot fight
and this outsider won't dare to kill me.
I will forge my name here !
Hey kid,
you can still kneel and beg for mercy now.
The rules say that
if you harm me,
you'll be executed !
You're noisy...
Let's see how long you can dodge !
You aren't
a match for me.
Ao Di isn't that strong.
If it was Shi Xiao,
he wouldn't have lasted a single move.
Exactly !
How ridiculous !
In order to win,
he...
he actually removed his armor
to use his Life-artifact !
How could you possibly
block my Demon Beast's Blood God Arrow !?
You...
You dare !?
Your Excellency,
he broke the rules !
Wang Lin !
You have some nerve !
The rules say I can't kill a Demon General.
But...
isn't he still alive ?
You severed his meridians
and crippled him !
And ?
You won
this duel !
Ao Di's helper !
I... forfeit !
I forfeit !
He forfeited just like that ?
Yeah...
1 day later
The winner is Mo Lihai.
After 4 matches,
Mo Lihai advances to the second round.
Brother Wang, go back to the residence to rest.
I'll still rely on you for the later rounds.
That guy just bullies people in the name of the Emperor.
Once Brother Wang gains the Demon Emperor's favor,
he won't dare to say a word !
Excuse me, excuse me.
For her to seat beside the Demon Emperor...
Could she be...
The Demon Emperor's Sword Spirit !?
Note: Little Black = Number Four
Master,
let Little Xu handle this !
Little Black taught me a secret move,
I guarantee I can make the opponent scram !
Using him to buy a little time
is a decent plan.
The Sword Spirit of the Demon Emperor is actually...
such a pretty little girl !
Little beauty, Brother Xu is coming to dote on you !
What a filthy creature !
Get away !
Note: Xu Liguo had fallen in love with the soul fragment of Mei Ji (in the artifact of the Giant Demon Clan Ancestor)
Back then, because of that fiend, my love was denied.
Fortunately, the heavens are blessing me today !
Don't be like that,
we're both Sword Spirits.
We are fated for each other.
Disgusting !
Don't go !
You haven't finished your candied hawthorn yet !
Note: candied hawthorn is the snack she was eating, it has a connotation of romance.
My... my...
My little beauty !!!
My little beauty and I were about to get together
and you...
you tore us apart !
Wang Lin,
back then, you denied my love for the beauty in that artifact,
and now you're stopping me from pursuing this love !
You're just jealous of my dashing looks
because you're all alone
and can't stand to see others happy !
Is that all ?
I'm not done !
Unless you let me out to find the little beauty I...
My little beauty !
Big brother is coming !
As expected...
My old restriction isn't strong enough to restrain him.
Wang Lin...
You're forcing my hand !
Little Black,
come out !
Release the restriction immediately
or else...
The fiend's strength is getting more and more terrifying...
But I will fight
for my love !
Little Black !
Mas...
Master...
Are you done ?
Master's cultivation is heavenly,
Little Xu will never dare to betray you again.
Master is so wise !
I swear I'll never go find the little beauty again.
Sky Demon City is filled with powerful experts.
Did you think no one would see you ?
With your strength,
they would wipe out your consciousness
and enslave you into a sword.
I guess I'm a Sword Spirit,
which sword I'm in doesn't matter...
Master is right !
From now on, Little Xu will definitely get rid of his desires
and will never have wicked thoughts !
Both you and the half-moon blade
have learned quite a few skills.
Little Black has many techniques.
It can conceal its aura,
and can even enhance the strength of a celestial sword.
Cultivating them isn't easy...
Master, please be merciful and let it stay.
My little beauty...
I wonder when we will meet again...
Lord Wang,
someone wishes to see you in the courtyard.
The name of fellow cultivator Wang
was already famous back on planet Tian Yun.
I came here to express my gratitude.
In today's Demon General competition
you helped us understand
how a cultivator should be.
You flatter me.
In the Demon Spirit Land,
our lives are worthless.
Demon Generals cannot be killed
but helpers can be slaughtered.
Only fellow cultivator Wang
was able to repay them for that.
Although military merit is important,
we must be able to live through it !
But this competition
is just a way for them
to sharpen their blades.
Cultivators should act according to the situation,
not obstinate over futile things.
We have decided to withdraw from the competition.
We came specially to bid farewell to fellow cultivator Wang.
The Demon Generals are watching me like tigers.
Jin Wuxu kept targeting me.
This rule that Demon Generals can't be killed
might as well be my death sentence.
Act according to the situation...
Perhaps...
they are right.
Ming Xuan,
continue.
From Qi Condensation all the way to Peak Late stage Soul Transformation,
which step
wasn't reached out of a desperate situation ?
Cultivators should act according to the situation,
not obstinate over futile things.
If I had followed the will of the heavens,
I wouldn't be alive today.
Withdrawing
is not an option,
it's a grave.
Defy the heavens with my actions.
Defy the heavens by cultivating.
Cultivate to defy.
Cultivate for freedom.
This is...
my Dao !
Defying
is my path to the Ascendant realm.
Such a Dao Heart...
Perhaps he is the person
the Ancestor has been waiting for.
Accept your fate and stay mortal
or defy it to become immortal !
The heavens can't shake my Dao Heart
so they will try to eradicate my existence !
They can destroy my body,
but they can't destroy my Dao Heart !
If the heavens want to kill me...
I will...
destroy the heavens !
Those who disturb my Ascendant breakthrough
must die !
Whoever wishes to kill me
shall be trapped in my Underworld River,
my own reincarnation cycle
free from the heavens and the earth !